（微妙的爆炸）
(subtle blast)
- 问答任务中的后处理步骤。
- The post-processing step in a question-answering task.
在做答题时，
When doing question answering,
初始数据集的处理
the processing of the initial dataset
意味着将示例拆分为多个功能，
implies splitting examples in several features,
其中可能包含也可能不包含答案。
which may or may not contain the answer.
通过模型传递这些特征
Passing those features through the model
将为我们提供开始和结束位置的 logits，
will give us logits for the start and end positions,
因为我们的标签是令牌的索引
since our labels are the indices of the tokens
对应于开始和结束的答案。
that correspond to the start and end the answer.
然后我们必须以某种方式将这些 logits 转换为答案，
We must then somehow convert those logits into an answer,
然后从每个功能给出的各种答案中选择一个
and then pick one of the various answers each feature gives
成为给定示例的答案。
to be the answer for a given example.
对于处理步骤，
For the processing step,
你应该参考下面链接的视频。
you should refer to the video linked below.
验证并没有太大的不同，
It's not very different for validation,
我们只需要添加几行来跟踪两件事：
we just need to add a few lines to keep track of two things:
而不是丢弃偏移映射，
instead of discarding the offset mappings,
我们保留它们，并在其中包含信息
we keep them, and also include in them the information
通过设置偏移量来确定上下文的位置
of where the context is by setting the offsets
特殊标记和无的问题。
of the special tokens and the question to None.
然后我们还跟踪每个功能的示例 ID，
Then we also keep track of the example ID for each feature,
能够映射回特征
to be able to map back feature
他们起源的例子。
to the examples that they originated from.
如果你不想计算验证损失，
If you don't want to compute the validation loss,
你不需要包含所有特殊代码
you won't need to include all the special code
我们用来创建标签的。
that we used to create the labels.
完成后，我们可以应用该预处理功能
With this done, we can apply that preprocessing function
使用映射方法。
using the map method.
我们在预处理中采用 SQUAD 数据集
We take the SQUAD dataset like in the preprocessing
用于问答视频。
for question-answering video.
一旦完成，下一步就是创建我们的模型。
Once this is done, the next step is to create our model.
我们使用后面的默认模型
We use the default model behind
这里的问答管道，
the question-answering pipeline here,
但你应该使用你想要评估的任何模型。
but you should use any model you want to evaluate.
使用 to_tf_dataset 方法，
With the to_tf_dataset method,
我们可以将处理过的数据集发送到 model.predict，
we can just sent our processed dataset to model.predict,
我们直接得到我们的开始和结束 logits
and we directly get our start and end logits
将整个数据集作为 NumPy 数组。
for the whole dataset as NumPy arrays.
完成后，我们就可以真正深入到后期处理中了。
With this done, we can really dive into the post-processing.
首先，我们需要一张从示例到功能的映射，
First, we'll need a map from example to features,
我们可以这样创建。
which we can create like this.
现在，对于后处理的主要部分，
Now, for the main part of the post-processing,
让我们看看如何从 logits 中提取答案。
let's see how to extract an answer from the logits.
我们可以只取最好的索引
We could just take the best index
对于开始和结束登录并完成，
for the start and end logits and be done,
但如果我们的模型预测了一些不可能的事情，
but if our model predicts something impossible,
就像问题中的标记，
like tokens in the questions,
我们将查看更多的 logits。
we will look at more of the logits.
请注意，在问答管道中，
Note that in the question-answering pipeline,
我们将分数归因于每个答案
we attributed the score to each answer
基于我们没有在这里计算的概率。
based on the probabilities, which we did not compute here.
在 logits 方面，我们有乘法
In terms of logits, the multiplication we had
在分数中成为加法。
in the scores becomes an addition.
为了走得快，我们不看
To go fast, we don't look
在所有可能的开始和结束日志中，
at all possible start and end logits,
但最好的 20 个。
but the 20 best ones.
我们忽略产生不可能答案的逻辑
We ignore the logits that spawn impossible answers
或回答太长。
or answer that are too long.
正如我们在预处理中看到的，
As we saw in the preprocessing,
标签 “0, 0” 对应于没有答案，
the label "0, 0" correspond to no answer,
否则我们使用偏移量
otherwise we use the offset
在上下文中得到答案。
to get the answer inside the context.
我们来看看预测答案
Let's have a look at the predicted answer
对于第一个功能，
for the first feature,
这是得分最高的答案，
which is the answer with the best score,
或自 SoftMax 以来最好的 logit 分数
or the best logit score since the SoftMax
是增函数。
is an increasing function.
模型做对了。
The model got it right.
接下来，我们只需要为每个示例循环这个，
Next, we just have to loop this for every example,
为每个选择具有最佳 logit 分数的答案
picking for each the answer with the best logit score
在示例生成的所有功能中。
in all the features the example generated.
现在你知道如何从模型预测中获得答案了。
Now you know how to get answers from your model predictions.
（微妙的爆炸）
(subtle blast)